[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This unit,  named after one of the main discoverers of electromagnetism, is the base unit of electrical current.", "correct_answer": "Ampere", "incorrect_answers": ["OHM", "Frequency", "Capacitor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Godzilla had his own comic book series produced by DC Comics.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1931 musical comedy Le Million, in which the storyline centers on a lottery ticket?", "correct_answer": "Rene Clair", "incorrect_answers": ["Ernest Lubitsch", "Josef von Sternberg", "Charlie Chaplin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The proper spelling of this insect\u2019s name is preying mantis even though it is commonly referred to as praying mantis.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Despite the fierce image movies have attributed to dinosaurs, approximately this percent of dinosaurs fed on plants and were quite peaceful.", "correct_answer": "65 %", "incorrect_answers": ["20 %", "52 %", "90 %"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are frogs reptiles?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the lucky winner of the Razzie Award for Worst Actor for 1998?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Bruce Willis for Mercury Rising", "Bruce Willis for Armageddon", "Bruce Willis for The Siege"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the context of construction, how long is a 2d nail?", "correct_answer": "1 inch", "incorrect_answers": ["1 foot", "20 cm", "1 cm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fruit of the poisonous Jerusalem cherry is very similar to which of these?", "correct_answer": "Cherry tomato", "incorrect_answers": ["Morello cherry", "Apricot", "Cranberry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these words means someone who believes the self is the most important thing ?", "correct_answer": "Egoist", "incorrect_answers": ["Narcissist", "A person with OCD", "Egotist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did the Treaty of Maastricht  result in?", "correct_answer": "The European Union was set up.", "incorrect_answers": ["The Hundreds Year War ended.", "World War II formally ended in Europe.", "The United Nations was established."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which World War One battles were the first ever fought by the Australian and New Zealand Army Corps (ANZAC) as a joint force?", "correct_answer": "Gallipoli battles", "incorrect_answers": ["Galicia battles", "Ghent battles", "Georgetown battles"]}]